Norn
It's the same hell I did
I have to help her whatever it takes
It doesn't matter if she hates me and Aisha
It doesn't matter if she hates it here and doesn't wanna live with us
She's my little sister
Excuse me
It's a big brother's job to protect his siblings
To never turn his back on them
Someone is going to pay
Oh, um, Mr. Grayrat, I'm sorry we're in the middle of class right now.
I won't take long. You have a few minutes, don't you?
But...
As I suspect you may have already noticed, one of your classmates has stopped showing up.
But what you may not know, that girl is my little sister, Norn.
I haven't been able to speak with her yet, so I don't have all the details.
But there are only so many reasons that a kid her age would stop coming to class.
I believe someone in this room is responsible for one of them.
Who was it? Who's bullying her?
Was it you? Or you? Or you?
Those involved, please step up. I'm not going to yell at you.
I just want you to understand that my sister was hurt and apologized to her.
And after that, I'll tear you limb from limb.
I don't care if they're the actual bullies or not.
Anyone who turned a blind eye is just as guilty.
Now fess up!
Oh, um...
Pardon me.
Yes?
Um, okay. Well, I, um...
I was actually talking to Norn the other day.
I see. You said something hurtful by accident, right?
No, nothing like that.
It's just, I've heard a lot of stories about you, Mr. Great Rat.
But Norn is more of an ordinary girl.
I just pointed out that you're pretty different from each other.
And she got really angry.
What?
That doesn't make any sense.
Norn doesn't want to be like me.
So why...
Oh...
Did something come to mind, ma'am?
Yes. One thing.
I was returning a homework assignment that she had done a bit poorly on.
And so is punishment.
You stripped her naked in the faculty office. Is that it?
No. Heavens.
I simply said to try harder next time.
That if she followed her big brother's example, she'd be doing well.
And...
She said she'd try, but she looked about ready to burst into tears.
Poor thing.
Wait.
Yeah, now that you mention it.
I may have said...
Me too.
It was my fault.
No wonder she couldn't stand it.
People have always compared her to Aisha.
Now they're doing it with a brother she hates.
Damn it.
I heard what happened.
Don't blame yourself, Rudy.
Too late for that.
But I guess I'll try.
Yeah, Meow. None of that is your fault, boss man.
Yeah, for sure.
You didn't do anything.
I appreciate it.
And thank you for letting me know about Norn.
Sorry I dragged you over to her classroom.
That was dumb.
And embarrassing.
There's nothing dumb about sticking up for your family, Meow.
I've got a little sister, too.
So I know how that stuff can be.
Meow, what a tough performance.
You got scary.
So, Meow what?
Are you gonna try to talk to her?
We could send a message for you.
I don't think that would do any good.
She hold herself up because of me.
Because of me.
She's a shut-in because of me.
Well, Lina and I could always drag her to class.
Yeah, easy.
If she stays in there too long, her brain will be goop.
Yup, you got that right.
Then she'll be as stupid as Lina.
Persina's right on the money, boss.
Meow.
What's that supposed to mean?
That her brain is goop.
People don't stop going outside because it's fun.
She's got a reason.
And us dragging her out won't change that.
Matter of fact, it's way more likely that'll just make the whole thing worse.
But, I don't know.
I can't just ignore this.
If she stays in there too long, I know I...
She'll regret it.
Rudy.
Hey, Rudy.
Think.
I have to do something.
But what?
Nothing ever helped me.
Rudy!
I mean, we're serious about helping out with your whole sister thing, you know.
Yeah, you're always looking out for us.
It's only fair.
That really is kind of you.
But I still don't...
Don't you worry about nothing, boss.
I got a great idea already.
The dorms sure cleared up fast.
What's the deal?
Princess Ariel's giving a speech in the dining hall.
Wait, are you for real?
Talk about impromptu.
Well, come on, or she's gonna start without us.
Rudy.
Well, we're a go.
The dorm is practically empty now.
Exactly as planned.
Ariel's speeches always draw a crowd.
Okay.
I'll sneak into the girl's wing and see if I can reach Norn.
Good.
Please give Princess Ariel my thanks.
And the other two?
In position.
And hey, I'm sorry I couldn't be more help.
What?
Well, I stopped by Norn's room earlier today to check up on her.
But she didn't want to see me either.
It's more than enough that you even tried.
Don't worry.
I'll work it out with Norn somehow.
Thanks for the inn.
You ready to roll?
Just watch where you're going next time.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Norn.
Hang in there.
I'm coming.
Made it, Meow.
Your sister's room is at the end of the hall on the right.
Norn, it's me, Rudeus.
Can I come in?
You awake?
Stay out.
Let me see.
No, you.
Now we're going to be...
After the inn I'll be...
Norton.
When I first became a shut-in, my older brother came to visit me like this.
He hit me with all kinds of common sense and reasonably sound arguments.
There are people out there who have it worse than you.
If you run away from all your problems, you'll be running forever.
It may hurt now, but the regret will hurt worse.
Then the bargaining.
You don't have to go back to school right away.
That can wait.
At least come out and have lunch with me.
I spit on all of it.
Didn't try to argue, didn't look at him, just ignored him.
Stayed totally silent till he was gone.
I convinced myself that someone like him couldn't possibly know how I felt.
I think now I know how he felt to some extent.
He was there for a long time, but eventually he left.
It's not hard to imagine why.
So I worry that if I back off now, Norn may stay in this room forever.
I can't just turn and run.
I won't.
Not this time.
you're doing your point.
I can only be réponse.
Brother.
I wonder...
I wonder, when exactly did I start to be afraid of him?
The first time we met, he punched my dad in the face.
The dad who'd kept me safe all that time.
Who always put me first.
Who loved me more than anything.
Stop it!
Leave him alone!
I wasn't about to accept a monster like that as part of my family.
I wasn't scared of him then.
I just hated him.
And when I finally saw him again, he'd been out getting drunk with some woman hanging all over him.
My dad is out there looking everywhere for my mom.
He could be someplace dangerous.
And there he was, looking like he couldn't be happier.
No one here cares about us.
So I just have to make sure I don't upset them.
I don't want them to kick me out.
It's too cold.
I won't make it.
Okay then.
I'll try living in the dorm.
Not what I expected, but...
Don't let her!
Dad told us we had to come here and live with our big brother!
If you're sure, then yeah.
I think we can arrange that.
That's not fair!
Why isn't he getting angry?
I thought he'd yell at me for being selfish.
Maybe he's just not interested in me at all.
Yeah, I bet I'm in his way.
For some reason, that makes me feel a little sad.
It's a pleasure to meet all of you.
My name is Norn Greyrat.
Greyrat?
Like those Greyrats?
Hey Norn, are you related to Rudeus Greyrat by chance?
I am.
The Rudeus?
He's the strongest guy in the school.
That is so cool!
Sister, huh?
What was it like growing up with him?
Like, does he teach you magic and stuff?
Oh, I bet so.
You must be some kind of magical genius yourself.
Your brother is incredible.
I mean, he's so talented.
You're so lucky.
I wish I had a brother even half as cool as you do.
Your name is...
Norn Greyrat.
Excuse me.
Hey, you're Rudeus' little sister, aren't you?
I am.
My name is Norn.
Oh, perfect.
We've been looking all over for you
because he helped us learn some magic a little while back.
Would you tell him we said thanks again?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
That's all right.
It's your first assignment.
You just got here.
I'm sure you'll follow in your brother's footsteps soon enough.
No, I won't.
I won't.
Hey.
Yes?
Tell me something about your brother.
I don't want to.
Are you curious about your brother hanging around with Princess Ariel?
You needn't worry about it.
Despite appearances, your brother is...
I don't care.
You needn't worry about your brother hanging around with Princess Ariel.
Seriously?
What were you thinking?
I got in trouble with the Princess for that.
Ah, look.
It's Rudeus.
Did I tell you I talked to him one time?
What?
Ah, lucky.
Why does everyone get like this about him?
No, I can't.
What?
I just don't understand him.
Because I worry.
Hey, cut him some slack.
I don't want to. I hate him.
Well, don't do that.
Rudy's had it rough.
Dad said stuff like that all the time.
I guess I was too little to understand what he meant.
But now I think I kind of get it.
Maybe he was having a hard time about something.
Maybe we're actually more alike than I thought.
But what am I supposed to do about it?
How do I just talk things out with him now?
How did Dad make up with him?
I don't know.
I don't know and no one here will help me.
What's wrong?
I want to go back to Eastport and see my dad.
You dislike Rudeus that much, do you?
I do.
I can see why.
But he's more than your poor first impression of him.
He's strong, clever.
A warrior worthy of respect.
That doesn't make sense.
It will someday when you're older.
The next time you see him, keep your chin up and don't run.
Family bonds can nearly always be mended.
If you don't believe me, just remember this.
Your father didn't run from him, did he?
Rudeus.
Lorne, I'm sorry.
You've had it rough from the minute you got here.
You finally got a fresh start.
And it turned out like this because of me.
I don't know what to say.
It's like, or it is, I just don't know you.
I realize how hard this must be, but I don't know what I can do to help.
But, I do know, I want to be here for you.
I want to understand you.
So, do you mind if I stay?
He really is just like my dad.
I can't be scared of that.
He was never going to hit me at all, was he?
And I know he won't hit dad anymore either.
So, I guess I should.
I should.
Hey, and good morning, big brother.
Oh, hello.
Good morning, Lorne.
And to you as well, Sophie.
You look really nice.
Thanks.
It's so good to see you, Lorne.
Oh, look at her.
She's so much more cheerful since you talked to her.
Not my doing.
I barely said anything at all.
Lorne never told me what she was upset about or what she'd been feeling.
And I may never know.
She just cried for a long time.
And yet...
Something tells me she's going to be all right.
She must have worked through those tough feelings on her own.
Atta girl.
At ten, she pulled off something I was never able to manage in my past life.
If I'd been more like her back then, I wonder.
Rudy?
Hey, what's the matter?
Nothing.
Just thinking.
I can't change my past.
I can't fix the relationships I broke.
And I'll never know how my family really felt back then.
But I still feel like something that was stuck between my teeth for a long time finally broke free.
I take it you'll be all right now, too?
Well, we should probably get going.
We still need to thank Princess Ariel and get her up to speed.
Yeah.
I need to find Lini and Persina, too.
If Nanahoshi does manage to return to our old world someday, I'll have to ask her to get a message to my brother.
I'm sorry for everything I put you through back then.
And thank you.
La-ya-la-ya-la